Fanelesbonge Nduduzo Zondi

City of Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa



nduduzo@yellogarden.co.za



0681384241



linkedin.com/in/nduduzo-f-zondi-01a54516b



https://bit.ly/3iHwlht

Summary

I'm a software developer with a keen aptitude for tinkering, conceptual thinking, and problem-solving. I'm familiar with languages like Java, Typescript, and Python.

I like being involved in projects that allow me to learn new skills and expand my knowledge and experience with different tools.

Experience



Team mentor

WeThinkCode

May 2022 - Aug 2022 (4 months)

This was volunteer work. I mentored boot camp students with their team projects to ensure they understood coursework and deliverables. Provided insight on technical concepts needed to complete their work, and worked with them as a team to demonstrate collaboration.

Frontend Developer

Yello Garden

Dec 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Yello Garden is a startup I co-founded. I'm involved in taking projects from concept to something usable by the public. I use React and Vue to build high-performing, interactive user experiences for web applications that are optimized for all types of devices.

Our clients come from various industries:

- E-commerce
- Retail
- Finance



Technical Support Specialist

WeThinkCode

May 2022 - Oct 2022 (6 months)

I used Ansible and did a lot of shell scripting to automate setting up and configuring Linux OS on computers connected to the same network.

Some of the work I performed included the following:

- Linux OS basic configuration
- Linux OS network configuration
- Linux OS user management
- Linux OS troubleshooting

Education

we think

WeThinkCode

NQF Level 5 (Systems development), Computer Software Engineering

Sep 2021 - May 2023

Involved in a fast-paced peer-to-peer learning environment. Learning full-stack software engineering by building projects iteratively. Some of the tools I work with include:

- Java
- Python
- SQL
- Relational Database Management Systems
- Git
- GitLab
- Linux

Some of the concepts learned:

- Agile development
- Collaboration
- CI/CD pipelines
- Software testing
- Concurrency & threading
- Network programming
- Application performance & scalability

Licenses & Certifications

Modernizing Java EE Applications - IBM

0aec0261c0104ed7af7423fa638d7d93

Docker Essentials - IBM

06ef3248790f4ed9a527dd7400ea0867

Skills

TypeScript • JavaScript • Java • Python (Programming Language) • Node.js • React.js • SASS • REST APIs • PostgreSQL • Shell Scripting